{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"56.1/0.03",
			"answer":"56.1/0.03",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.084/0.04",
			"answer":"0.084/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"420/0.6",
			"answer":"420/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.08/0.3",
			"answer":"7.08/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"63.6/0.02",
			"answer":"63.6/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.76/0.09",
			"answer":"5.76/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"640/8",
			"answer":"640/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"960/0.6",
			"answer":"960/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"721/7",
			"answer":"721/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"89.6/7",
			"answer":"89.6/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}